freeiq.com 2009-02-10

# Free IQ - The Marketplace for Ideas.

Simply stated, here at FreeIQ.com we hate spam as much as you do. Therefore, we will not sell, lease or rent your e-mail address to anyone. Period.

Now for the fine print, to keep the lawyers happy...

## Collection of Your Personal Information

In order to access some Free IQ services, you will be asked to sign in with an e-mail address and password, which form the basis of your account. As part of creating your account, you may also be requested to provide questions and secret answers, which we use to help verify your identity and assist in resetting your password, as well as an alternate email address. Finally, a unique affiliate ID number may be assigned to your account which will be used to identify your account and associated information.

To access some Free IQ products and services we ask you to provide personal information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. We may also collect demographic information, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites. If you choose to make a purchase or sign up for a paid subscription service, we will ask for additional information, such as your credit card number and billing address, which is used to create a Free IQ billing account.

We may collect information about your visit, including the pages you view, the links you click and other actions taken in connection with Free IQ sites and services. We also collect certain standard information that your browser sends to every website you visit, such as your IP address, browser type and language, access times and referring website addresses.

When you receive newsletters, RSS feeds, or promotional e-mail from Free IQ, we may use web beacons (described below), customized links or similar technologies to determine whether the e-mail has been opened and which links you click in order to provide you more focused e-mail communications or other information.

In order to offer you a more consistent and personalized experience in your interactions with Free IQ, information collected through one Free IQ service may be combined with information obtained through other Free IQ services. We may also supplement the information we collect with information obtained from other companies. For example, we may use services from other companies that enable us to derive a general geographic area based on your IP address in order to customize certain services to your geographic area.

## Use of Your Personal Information

Free IQ collects and uses your personal information to operate and improve its sites and deliver the services or carry out the transactions you have requested. These uses may include providing you with more effective customer service; making the products or services easier to use by eliminating the need for you to repeatedly enter the same information; performing research and analysis aimed at improving our products, services and technologies; and displaying content and advertising that are customized to your interests and preferences.

We also use your personal information to communicate with you. We may send certain mandatory service communications such as welcome letters, billing reminders, affiliate payments, affiliate promotional opportunities, information on technical service issues, and security announcements. We may also occasionally send you product surveys or promotional mailings to inform you of other products or services available from Free IQ and its affiliates.

Personal information collected on Free IQ sites and services may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Free IQ or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using a Free IQ site or service, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. We may also aggregate personal information (such as age) with other similar information from other users, and share your data with other parties, as long as the information shared with third parties is not personally identifiable to you (in other words, kept anonymous). 

## Sharing of Your Personal Information

Except as described in this statement, we will not disclose your personal information outside of Free IQ and its controlled subsidiaries and affiliates without your consent. Some Free IQ pages allow you to choose to share your personal information with select Free IQ partners so that they can contact you about their products, services or offers. See the Communication Preferences section below for more information.

Some Free IQ services may be co-branded and offered in conjunction with another company. If you register for or use such services, both Free IQ and the other company may receive information collected in conjunction with the co-branded services.

We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as handling the processing and delivery of mailings, providing customer support, data mining, ad delivery, hosting websites, processing transactions, or performing statistical analysis of our services. Those companies will be permitted to obtain only the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information and are prohibited from using it for any other purpose.

When you purchase products on Free IQ that are sold by other providers, that provider will be supplied with your contact information for shipping and contact purposes, and the usage of that information will be subject to that provider's privacy policies.

When you sign up to join a content provider's mailing list, that provider will receive your name and email address, the usage of which will be subject to that provider's privacy policies.

We may access and/or disclose your personal information if we believe such action is necessary to: (a) comply with the law or legal process served on Free IQ; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Free IQ (including the enforcement of our agreements); or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Free IQ services or members of the public.

## Accessing Your Personal Information

You may have the ability to view or edit the personal information retained by Free IQ online. In order to help prevent your personal information from being viewed by others, you will be required to sign in with your account information (username and password). You can access and update your profile on FreeIQ.com by logging into your account and clicking the Personal Info link. 

## Communication Preferences

You can stop the delivery of future promotional e-mail from Free IQ sites and services by following the specific instructions in the e-mail you receive.

These communication choices do not apply to mandatory service communications that are considered part of certain Free IQ services, which you may receive periodically unless you cancel the service.

## Security of Your Personal Information

Free IQ is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer systems with limited access, which are located in controlled facilities. When we transmit highly confidential information (such as a credit card number or password) over the Internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

If a password is used to help protect your accounts and personal information, it is your responsibility to keep your password confidential. Do not share this information with anyone. If you are sharing a computer with anyone you should always choose to log out before leaving a site or service to protect access to your information from subsequent users.

## Collection and Use of Children's Personal Information

Many Free IQ sites are intended for general audiences and do not knowingly collect any personal information from children. When a Free IQ site does collect age information, and users identify themselves as under 13, the site will block such users from providing personal information. We will not knowingly ask children under the age of 13 to provide more information than is reasonably necessary to provide our services.

We encourage you to talk with your children about communicating with strangers and disclosing personal information online. 

## Use of Cookies

Free IQ websites use "cookies" to enable you to sign in to our services and to help personalize your online experience. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies contain information that can later be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer.

Free IQ websites use cookies to store your preferences and other information on your computer in order to save you time by eliminating the need to repeatedly enter the same information and to display your personalized content and appropriate advertising on your later visits to these sites.

When you sign in to a site using your account, Free IQ stores your unique account information in an encrypted cookie on your hard disk. This cookie allows you to move from page to page at the site without having to sign in again on each page. 

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use other interactive features of Free IQ sites and services that depend on cookies.

## Use of Web Beacons

Free IQ Web pages may contain electronic images known as Web beacons - sometimes called single-pixel gifs - that may be used to assist in delivering cookies on our sites and allow us to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. We may include Web beacons in promotional e-mail messages or our newsletters in order to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon.

Free IQ may also employ Web beacons from third parties in order to help us compile aggregated statistics and determine the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns. We prohibit Web beacons on our sites from being used by third parties to collect or access your personal information.

Finally, we may work with other companies that advertise on Free IQ sites to place Web beacons on their sites in order to allow us to develop statistics on how often clicking on an advertisement on a Free IQ site results in a purchase or other action on the advertiser's site.

## Use of Third Party Ad Networks

The majority of the online banner advertisements you see on Free IQ Web pages are displayed by Free IQ. However, we may allow other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to display advertisements on Free IQ Web pages. Some of these ad networks may place a persistent cookie on your computer in order to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad networks may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. Free IQ does not have access to the cookies that may be placed by the third-party ad servers or ad networks.

Free IQ may maintain relationships with a number of the third-party ad networks currently operating such as: Avenue A; BlueStreak; DoubleClick; Mediaplex; Pointroll; RealMedia; TangoZebra; and Unicast. Those ad networks that use persistent cookies may offer you a way to opt out of ad targeting. You may find more information at the website of either the individual ad network or the Network Advertising Initiative.

## Controlling "Spam" or Unsolicited E-mail

Free IQ is concerned about controlling unsolicited commercial e-mail, or "spam." Free IQ has a strict Anti-Spam Policy prohibiting the use of email addresses in our database to send spam. Free IQ will not sell, lease or rent its e-mail subscriber lists to third parties. 

## Enforcement of This Privacy Statement

If you have questions regarding this statement, you should contact us by using our Web form. 

## Changes to This Privacy Statement

We will occasionally update this privacy statement to reflect changes in our services and customer feedback. When we post changes to this Statement, we will revise the "last updated" date at the top of this statement. If there are material changes to this statement or in how Free IQ will use your personal information, we will notify you either by prominently posting a notice of such changes to your login screen prior to implementing the change or by directly sending you a notification. In case of change, you will have the ability to opt-out if you object to the change. If you do not opt-out within 30 days of notification, the new privacy policy changes will apply to your account as if you had expressly opted in under the new privacy policy. We encourage you to periodically review this statement to be informed of how Free IQ is protecting your information.

## Contacting Us

Free IQ welcomes your comments regarding this privacy statement. If you have questions about this statement or believe that we have not adhered to it, please contact us by using our Web form.

Free IQ Corporation, 6420 Atlantic Blvd, Suite 145, Norcross, GA 30071, U.S.A.
